katebush.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy policy | Kate Bush

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Noble and Brite Ltd (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

 **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  1. Information that you provide when you register to become a user or otherwise fill in forms on our site [www.katebush.com](http://www.katebush.com/ "www.katebush.com") (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion and when you report a problem with our site.
  2. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  3. We or our agents on our behalf may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  4. Details of any transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders.
  5. Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access. 
  6. Over time you may provide or we will ask you to provide additional information which will extend your personal profile so we can increase our ability to ensure relevance of any messaging.  You may choose to provide additional information to help this process.

 **IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  1. To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  2. To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.
  3. To speed up your searches.
  4. To recognise you when you return to our site. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system may issue cookies when you log on to our site.

 **WHERE WE STORE PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (”EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.  We will endeavour to take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

 **USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  1. To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  2. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  3. To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  4. To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  5. To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form).

 **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  1. In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  2. If Noble and Brite Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  3. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Noble and Brite Ltd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [admin@katebush.com](mailto:admin@katebush.com).

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **INTERNET AWARENESS**

Whenever you voluntarily post personal information in public areas, like journals, web-blogs, reviews, message boards, and forums, you should be aware that this information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by others to send you unsolicited communications.  Please exercise discretion in deciding what information you disclose.

 **MINORS**

Our policy is to request that “Minors” (the age of Minors is determined by local laws where you reside) do not make purchases or engage in other legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless permitted by applicable local law.

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

 **CONTACT**

If you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website you can contact us by emailing [admin@katebush.com](mailto:admin@katebush.com) or by writing to katebush.com c/o Ym&U Business Management Limited, 4th Floor, 180 Great Portland Street, London, W1W 5QZ, UK.
